If you want a perfume that conveys both
elegance and refreshment, you have to go
with the brand new Sparkling Royal by
Kilian Paris from the Cocktails
collection. This smells like a very
luxurious French aperitif. You have the
blackcurrant in the opening, the rose,
the mint, the lemon. It's so bright and
refreshing in the opening, but then it
settles into this elegant and romantic
heart on account of the rose, and it
dries down into this delicious roasted
tonka bean accord. This is a beautiful
night out and evening scent. It is built
for those elegant evenings. If you're
wearing a beautiful dress, or if you're
a gentleman wearing a really nice suit
and tie, this is an incredibly unisex
fragrance, and it's incredibly elegant
as well. If you're looking for something
that embodies class and refinement, you
definitely have to go with the brand new
Sparkling Royal by Kilian Paris.